

OBJECTIVE

Endeavour to meet the challenging qualities of the industry by contributing my dexterity, consistency and hence developing my potential to organizational standards.

Around 2.9 years of experience in IT industry.

Multi-faceted individual with 1.4 years of experience in web development, 1.8 years of experience in US Staffing recruiting, 3 months of experience in Business Process Outsourcing.



ADDRESS

A-1, Anandam Apts, VCS Nagar, 2nd ST,GN Mills Post, Coimbatore – 641029, Tamil Nadu



PHONE

+91 8015619368



EMAIL

ashwinprasad698@gmail.com



WEBSITE

ashwindz11.github.io

EXPERIENCE

November 2017 – Present Front End Developer • FPS Animations Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu Responsibilities:

- Create, design and maintain dynamic website of the clients and of the company.
- Worked on HTML and CSS for the front-end part of the page.
- Used JavaScript for the user interaction.
- Worked on MySQL to maintain the database.
- Used CSS frameworks like Bootstrap for the better UI designs.
- Worked on server side languages like PHP for client-server interaction like Contact forms.
- Used Google Map API keys for specifying the locations.

August 2016 – April 2018 Technical Recruiter • Tekishub Consulting Services Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu Responsibilities:

- Responsible for resourcing, submitting resumes on assigned requirements and recruiting.
- Scheduling and organizing the interviews as per clients and Technical people requests.
- Responsible for interviewing, hiring decisions, candidate Salary negotiation, offers and declines.
- ♦ Worked on C2C, W2 and 1099 with different types of Visas like H1B, GC, EAD, USC.
- ◆ Worked with Implementation Partners and Direct Clients as well.
- ◆ Experienced in Boolean Search in various job portals like Dice, Career Builders, Monster and
- ♦ Ladders.
- Recruiting talent through various sources, which included internet (Job Portals), headhunting, advertisements, referrals, networking and vendors (Placement companies).
- Dealing with vendors for quality profiles and best speed measurement.
- Interaction with Resource Managers and technical people for requirement Gathering, technical screening for huge nos of IT contract staff.
- Targeting companies & closing the position with the time frame.
- Handling initial round of HR interviews in order to judge the candidate's suitability, Attitude,

- Academic & professional qualification, experience, communication skills etc, before forwarding to client and Technical people.
- Handled complete Recruitment Life Cycle Sourcing, Shortlisting Profiles, Candidates Tracking,
- ♦ Follow-ups, HR interviews and Reference checks

June 2016 – August 2016 Process Associate • KGiSL Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu Responsibilities:

- Attending the incoming calls from the customer and solving their queries.
- Provide the customers the information about the ongoing offers with the product demanded by them to improve sale productivity.
- Carefully note down the customer credit card number.
- Carefully verify the purchase order
- Make a note of date of delivery and the place of delivery with the customer.

EDUCATION

Info Institute of Engineering, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu Bachelors in Computer Science Engineering [2012 – 2016]

CERTIFICATIONS

- ♦ HTML Level 1 Certificate by Cambridge Certification Authority.
- ♦ CSS Level 1 Certificate by Cambridge Certification Authority.
- JavaScript Level 1 Certificate by Cambridge Certification Authority.
- ♦ PHP Level 1 Certificate by Cambridge Certification Authority.
- ♦ MySQL Level 1 Certificate by Cambridge Certification Authority.
- JQuery Level 1 Certificate by Cambridge Certification Authority.
- ♦ Google Digital Unlocked The Online Marketing Fundamentals
- freeCodeCamp -Front End Development Program
 Udacity Google India Scholarship Program
- ♦ IBM Blockchain Essentials

SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | JQuery | Bootstrap | Materialize | Wordpress | PHP | MySQL | Wireframe | UI/UX Design | MS Office | Git | SEO |

Recruiting | ATS | VTS | Human Resource

REFERENCES

[Available upon request.]